<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>CASPDBA</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>CASPDBA</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>PLEASE READ: Your CA Seller&apos;s Permit Order [#        ]</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName},

If you have already received your California State Board of Equalization Seller’s Permit, please disregard this email. If not, read on.

The California Board of Equalization (BOE) recently changed their process for applying for a seller’s permit to electronic registration and will no longer accept paper applications by mail. Because of this, we need to collect more information from you to complete your order.

Please call us as soon as possible to provide the following information:

1.	Contact information for all business owners, including:

a.	Full name
b.	Home address
c.	Phone number
d.	Date of birth
e.	Driver’s license number and state of issue
f.	Social Security number;


2.	Names and phone numbers of personal references;
3.	Name, address and phone numbers of all suppliers;
4.	Products purchased from all suppliers;
5.	NAICS code (go to http://www.naics.com/search.htm to search for the code for your primary business activity);
6.	Name and contact information for the person who will be maintaining the company’s books and records;
7.	Name and contact information for the person who can answer questions about the company’s business activities.

In order for us to complete your order in a timely manner, please call us as soon as possible at (800) 773-0888 Monday–Friday from 6 a.m.–7 p.m. PT.

We appreciate your prompt attention to this matter and look forward to hearing from you soon.

Best regards,

The LegalZoom Team




This is a service email related to your LegalZoom account. For more information about how LegalZoom uses your information, please see the Privacy Policy: http://www.legalzoom.com/privacy-policy-popup.html

LegalZoom provides access to independent attorneys and self-help services at your specific direction. We are not a law firm or a substitute for an attorney or law firm. Prices, features, terms and conditions are subject to change without notice.  LegalZoom is located at 9900 Spectrum Drive, Austin, TX 78717. 

Please add services@emails.legalzoom.com to your address book. 

This email was sent to: {!Contact.Email} 

  

© LegalZoom.com, Inc. All rights reserved.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
