<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>false</available>
    <description>rabsi</description>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <name>Registered Agent (Stand Alone)</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Registered Agent (Stand Alone)</subject>
    <textOnly>Dear {!Contact.FirstName} {!Contact.LastName},

Thank you for contacting LegalZoom for your business services needs. In regard to your inquiry, LegalZoom can assist you to serve as the Registered Agent for your company. 

The Registered Agent is responsible for receiving correspondence and legal notices on behalf of the company. The Registered Agent must be an adult with a physical street address in the state of the [Corporation?s/LLC?s] formation at which they are present during normal business hours. With LegalZoom&apos;s Registered Agent service, you will have additional privacy as the name and address of the Registered Agent is public information. LegalZoom will also filter out unsolicited mail and forward any official correspondence to you, ensuring that you will receive important documents in a timely manner. Additionally, you will be provided with a LegalZoom Compliance Calendar that notifies you of any upcoming filings required to maintain your company.

For your convenience, I have provided the Registered Agent services fee and the link to sign up below.

Registered Agent Services | $159.00 per year

TO GET STARTED:
http://www.legalzoom.com/additional-business-services/registered-agent-services.html

Please feel free to contact us at (888) 381-8758 if you have any further questions.  Our Business Formations Team business hours are {!snippetVariable.bizbsi_hours}.


Best regards,

{!User.FirstName} {!User.LastName} 
{!User.Title} 
{!User.CompanyName}
{!User.Address}
{!User.Phone} ext. {!User.Extension}


This is a service email related to your LegalZoom account. For more information about how LegalZoom uses your information, please see the Privacy Policy: http://www.legalzoom.com/privacy-policy-popup.html

LegalZoom provides access to independent attorneys and self-help services at your specific direction. We are not a law firm or a substitute for an attorney or law firm. Prices, features, terms and conditions are subject to change without notice.  LegalZoom is located at 9900 Spectrum Drive, Austin, TX 78717. 

Please add services@emails.legalzoom.com to your address book. 

This email was sent to: {!Contact.Email} 

  

© LegalZoom.com, Inc. All rights reserved.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
</EmailTemplate>
